The students are now asking Lily some questions after her talk.
Listen and complete the summary of Lily's answers below. Hi, Lily.
Thank you for sharing your English learning experience with us.
I have a question.
How important do you think pronunciation is?
Well, pronunciation is a big part of learning a language.
If you get the pronunciation wrong, people may not understand you.
Good pronunciation takes lots of practice, and doing just a little bit every day will be a big help.
Difficult to study grammar.
Yes, grammar can be hard to learn, but it is important.
We need the rules of a language to make sentences.
Try to write something in English every day.
Can reading help us improve our English too?
Yes, but it's important to read often.
Start by reading easy texts and then slowly move on to more difficult ones.
You don't have to understand every word.
The more you read, the more you'll understand.